
Name                                                                             Result Detail
----                                                                             ------ ------
Repeated snapshots reuse one verified bypass without adding routes or log floods PASS         
New endpoints produce one periodic summary instead of per-IP normal warnings     PASS         
Persistent captured socket is escalated but warning is rate-limited              PASS         
Unused owned routes are retired after the quiet period                           PASS         
An empty peer snapshot cannot prune owned routes                                 PASS         
Borrowed routes are never removed by retirement                                  PASS         
Changed owned route metric is rejected, not overwritten                          PASS         
Adapter identity changes are rejected before adding a route                      PASS         
Remembered endpoint is preinstalled on the fresh session gateway                 PASS         
Wrong image identity cannot seed the endpoint cache                              PASS         
Old and future endpoint records are ignored                                      PASS         
Unsafe cache address classes are excluded                                        PASS         
Cache serialization drops old overflow entries rather than growing unbounded     PASS         
Actual selected route is required: Competitor                                    PASS         
Actual selected route is required: WrongGateway                                  PASS         
Actual selected route is required: Ambiguous                                     PASS         
Actual selected route is required: Missing                                       PASS         
Actual selected route is required: QueryFailure                                  PASS         
Borrowed route metric changes that select another path are refused               PASS         
Failed retirement preserves route journal and registry for another attempt       PASS         
Exceptional bypass conditions fail without foreign deletion: Down                PASS         
Exceptional bypass conditions fail without foreign deletion: NotHardware         PASS         
Exceptional bypass conditions fail without foreign deletion: RouteQuery          PASS         
Exceptional bypass conditions fail without foreign deletion: AddFailure          PASS         
Combined interface and route metrics determine the selected path                 PASS         
A higher total metric competitor permits the intended physical route             PASS         
Gateway changes are rejected before installing a stale bypass                    PASS         
Actual route cleanup retains ownership on uncertainty: AdapterChanged            PASS         
Actual route cleanup retains ownership on uncertainty: MetricChanged             PASS         
Actual route cleanup retains ownership on uncertainty: RemovalUnconfirmed        PASS         
Actual route cleanup retains ownership on uncertainty: RemovalSuccess            PASS         
Actual route cleanup retains ownership on uncertainty: AlreadyAbsent             PASS         
Actual route creation journals only newly owned resources: Borrowed              PASS         
Actual route creation journals only newly owned resources: Added                 PASS         
Actual route creation journals only newly owned resources: AddFailure            PASS         


